let squidGameQuestions = [
	{
		question:" how many people took part in the games?",
		choiceA: "486",
		choiceB: "476",
		choiceC: "456",
		choiceD: "499",
		correctAnswer: "456"
	},
  {
		question: "What was the correct order the games were played in?",
		choiceA: "Red Light, Green Light, Honeycomb, Tug of War, Marbles, Stepping Stones, Squid Game",
		choiceB: "Red Light, Green Light, Tug of War, Marbles, Honeycomb, Stepping Stones, Squid Game",
		choiceC: "Honeycomb, Red Light, Green Light, Stepping Stones, Marbles, Tug of War, Squid Game",
		choiceD: "Red Light, Green Light, Tug of War, Honeycomb, Marbles, Stepping Stones, Squid Game", 
		correctAnswer: "Red Light, Green Light, Honeycomb, Tug of War, Marbles, Stepping Stones, Squid Game",
	},
  {
		question: "What number was Kang Sae-byeok?",
		choiceA: "047",
		choiceB: "103",
		choiceC: "067",
		choiceD: "301",
		correctAnswer: "067"
	},
  {
		question: "The police officer found out his brother had competed in the games, but in what year?",
		choiceA: "2018",
		choiceB: "2019",
		choiceC: "2016",
		choiceD: "2015",
		correctAnswer: "2015"
	},
  {
		question: "What did Gi-hun accidentally gift his daughter?",
		choiceA: "A gun", 
		choiceB: "A lighter",
		choiceC: "A knife",
		choiceD: "Matchsticks",
		correctAnswer: "A lighter"
	},
  {
		question: "What shape did the old man get to cut out in the honeycomb challenge?", 
		choiceA: "Triangle",
		choiceB: "Circle",
		choiceC: "Star", 
		choiceD: "Umbrella",
		correctAnswer:  "Star"
	},
		{
		question: "What happened to Deok-su when he went home during the Hell episode?", 
		choiceA: "He robbed from his boss", 
		choiceB: "He was stabbed", 
		choiceC: "He jumped from a bridge", 
		choiceD: "He got hit by a car",
		correctAnswer:  "He jumped from a bridge"
	},
		{
		question: "Which staff members have the most authority?",
		choiceA: "Circle",
		choiceB: "Square",
		choiceC: "Triangle", 
		choiceD: "Star",
		correctAnswer: "Square"
	},
		{
		question: "Which of the following is FALSE:",
		choiceA: "If the majority of players agree, the games can be stopped",
		choiceB: "Players are allowed to sit out of a game, with the Front Man's permission",
		choiceC: "All of the games are hidden in paintings around the dorm room",
		choiceD: "Players are allowed to go home after each game ", 
		correctAnswer: "Players are allowed to sit out of a game, with the Front Man's permission",
	},
		{
		question: "which of these was a meal given to the players?", 
		choiceA: "One avocado",
		choiceB: "One slice of bread", 
		choiceC: "One apple", 
		choiceD: "One boiled egg",
		correctAnswer: "One boiled egg"
	},
]